George,we can talk,but it can't take long.
George, 我们可以聊, 但它不能占用太久.
The baby's with Wendy.
宝宝和Wendy在一起.
No problem.
没问题
These are my ideas for the new brochure.
这些是我的点子  为新的宣传册
Ok. So... what's this?
Ok. So...这是什么?
It's the cover. I know that.
它是封面. 我知道那个.
What is this?
这个是什么?
Oh! It's a table,
Oh! 它是一个桌子,
and those are flowers
and 那些是花,
and that's a cup of coffee.
and 那是一杯咖啡.
And what's this here?
And 这是什么 这里?
It's a computer.
它是一个电脑.
That's a computer?
那是一个电脑?
I'm not an artist.
我不是一个艺术家
Ok.so what's the idea?
Ok.so点子是什么?
The Sheraton Boston is perfect for business meetings.
Sheraton Boston是完美的  对于商务会议.
Go on.
继续
Great lacation, Facilities.
很好的地理位置, 设备.
This is technology:computers and modems.
这是科技: 电脑和猫.
And that's us. We're the experts.
那是我们. 我们是专家.
It's a good thought,George.
它是一个好想法, Gorge.
But I can't understand the drawings.
但我不能理解图画
Use the computer. Use the graphics.
用电脑. 用绘图(软件)
Me?  -Why not?
我?  -为什么不?
Computers? They're a mystery!
电脑? 他们是一个迷!